<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>

<reviews>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2013-08-11T00:24:45Z</date>
<star_rating>1</star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Not much good that I can see. It will play my music, but no lyrics, no karaoke</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2013-03-26T17:56:53Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Brill (now) Use to play back trax solo singing. On old phone so no bulky laptop needed. Just needs a save feature to save whole playlist and files to s folder to setup ready on new device</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2013-08-15T09:40:05Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Very nice application So useful..... bought the pro one.. thanks</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2013-10-06T10:13:44Z</date>
<star_rating>4</star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>4 star Good Applications for Karaoke practices.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2013-11-09T11:22:24Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Love the app. Needs tempo adjuster Love the app but would be nice to be able to adjust the tempo.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2013-12-17T20:20:17Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Plays zipped cdg + mp3!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2013-12-12T19:15:10Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Love it top dog program Love it</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2013-12-31T20:28:37Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>worse Bad app</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2014-01-06T12:06:27Z</date>
<star_rating>1</star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Need quick Dir option Hard to put the SD directory to access cdg</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2014-02-05T16:59:06Z</date>
<star_rating>4</star_rating>
<review_title>Fantastic Karaoke App</review_title>
<review_text>Thank you, thank you,thank you! have been looking high and low for an app to let me play MY karaoke collection. I dont want to play from some of the crappy midi database online - I want to play my files with the lyrics - this app is the ONLY one that can read the LYC and txt files so I can easily add my own tracks and sing along! I also love that I can link my google drive account so I can access my online catalogue as well. A few things could improve this app - key and tempo changer would be wonderful and a widget would also be appreciated.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2014-02-24T11:53:36Z</date>
<star_rating>4</star_rating>
<review_title>Love the app</review_title>
<review_text>It would be better if there is a screen mirror option or chrome cast.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2014-03-27T15:35:56Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title>Best Midi Player Yet</review_title>
<review_text>The Best Yet! This is the best midi player app available and that is it's major strength and where it leaves the others far behind. Android or Mac. It has failed to play some tracks but there is sure to be another version among my 40,000 tracks. Editing is a breeze and changes can be saved! Great as a Karaoke machine and great for midi backing tracks. But while playing, editing and flicking between screens it vanished? Still playing the track with a BLACK screen and no response. This happened more than once on different tracks? This is on a Galaxy s4 LTE with Snapdragon 800 and Android 4.4 Kit Kat so they don't come much more powerful than that yet. It gets a bit hot with intensive play but most of us have a backup or resort to an unplugged set. It is a 5 star app for any musician using midi and it eliminates the need for editing software and masses of time to massage files. I can now tick "midi player app" off my bucket list and move on to the next item.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2014-05-19T14:59:53Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title>I like it!</review_title>
<review_text>Wish there was a way to get bigger fonts on the midi also the ability to have different background pictures fade in and out or even play a windows movie maker file in the background.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2014-06-01T09:47:59Z</date>
<star_rating>1</star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Very very bad after purchase doesn't allow you to refund so beware !!!!@@</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2014-07-02T15:09:14Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>As lm a karaoke die hard fan, this player app is a great pocket rocket of quality at a very low price. It works great with no glitches or hiccups, definitely worthy of a 5 star. I also got one for my 10 inch tablet. Cheers Steve L</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2014-10-19T23:38:32Z</date>
<star_rating>4</star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>This player is very good, haven't been able to work out the key changer, otherwise it's better than the rest.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2014-12-29T15:44:47Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title>i love it</review_title>
<review_text>owesome!!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-02-07T15:16:19Z</date>
<star_rating>3</star_rating>
<review_title>Almost there</review_title>
<review_text>Nice product, but lacks the option to search through subfolders with using Google Drive cloud services. Also the key change feature seems to have no effect on changing the key of the song. I can live without the key change feature for now, but searching through subfolders is a must on Google Drive cloud services. Please fix this feature. I love what you have done to date!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-02-17T00:13:32Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title>Just what I needed.</review_title>
<review_text>I plan to use it as a part-teaching device for a church choir. Using the drop-box import feature, it's a perfect tool!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-04-11T00:24:59Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title>Mike</review_title>
<review_text>Great for what I use it for</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-05-11T12:59:19Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title>Plays ZIPped mp3+G files!!</review_title>
<review_text>Easy-peasy! Not perfect - some brands' graphics (colors / backgrounds) are wonky but definitely readable. Playlist autoplay is kicka$$!! Great value! Buy it now!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-05-22T07:29:04Z</date>
<star_rating>5</star_rating>
<review_title>Good app</review_title>
<review_text>It let's me use my own library of tunes</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version>33</app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-06-10T14:34:39Z</date>
<star_rating>4</star_rating>
<review_title>Karaoke sing me</review_title>
<review_text>Nice little app, works with quite a few of my different formats and brands .</review_text>
</review>
</reviews>
