<reviews>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hi everyone. Thank you for participating this community. version 3.4.B.0.2 is just released!3.4 beta (3.4.B.0.2)Thank you for a lot of feedback for contents picker, we introduced our own special one. It's simple and easy.UIIn addition, you can share photos and videos to Movie Creator from other applications to create Highlight Movie.Movie CreatorPlease try these new features and enjoy</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Thank you for participating this community.Movie Creator 3.4 (3.4.A.0.3) is now available on Google Play!3.4Google PlayThis version includes some bug fixes and improvements from latest beta release.Your feedback is always welcome.Thanks and Enjoy!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Is this necessary? There's just one option after clicking on  create  button (first click). It could brings us directly into photo picker (excluded another  same  button but with different name(second click)).</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Ivan Ilini</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Here's an idea. I was working to create a video with Movie Creator with 2 movie clips to include and it made an video of 5second length. Overall my 2 clups would be like 20ish sec long. So why can't i pick a lenght of an clip on my own? This last new update is great deal towards the end product, which i personally want to be like iMovies on iPhone, great stuff to quickly edit and make a video on your phone without having to transfer over to PC for a detailed edit and overcomplication.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Thank you for participating in Beta trial.Movie Creator 3.2 (3.2.A.0.2) is now available on Google Play!3.2Google PlayThis release includes some bug fixes and improvements.Your feedback is always welcome.Thanks and Enjoy!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Shuvro Mojumder (Nero White)</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>It would be better if we have 4k video output support with the 1080p and 720p. And I am like to create videos of nature but i always need too edit that on my pc. It would be nice if this movie creator have some features of sony vegas pro 13. The track line to control the video and make it for myself just the way I wanted on my oPhone then it would be better</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>SiD Rhyte</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>All Z1 compact</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Teri Maria Cadano</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Good job! Now i can easily change the photos that i like to be included in video. How about to add photos? Can we do that? Is there a maximum pictures for each clip? Can we also edit the transition for each picture, for example the zooming part? Sorry for a lot of questions... Have a great day!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Homam Alhalabe</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>My photo xperia Z3</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Konstantin Z.</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Sai Lee</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I cant add more than one photo when creating new highlight manually, as it only allows one photo. is there another app i need to install so that it access the photos?? Tried using google photos with it, but wont allow.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>While picking photos/videos using album app (from sony), theres no possibility to choose more than one item. It would be fine to have this option because album order looks much more clearly form me instead of searching for photos/videos in folders.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Shuvro Mojumder (Nero White)</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Yash Kumar</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I'm new here</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>yaser rgb</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Good luck</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Roberto Choleva</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>How can I upload video clip?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Hung Tran</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>vicky gajjar</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Quang Nam - Viet Nam...^^</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Tabz Zaman</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>My cute son</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Would be great to be able to add more pictures in the movie creator and some more fancy editing functions. Otherwise love the app it makes some excellent movies</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Sometimes phoros are not ordered by time...</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Vishal Khanna</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hi everyone. Thank you for participating this community.We are happy to announce this update. New beta version of Movie Creator, version 3.2.B.0.0 is just released!3.2.B.0.0Finally, you can add your photo/video/note as you want. Let's touch and hold a photo/video to try this new feature.The UI and animation is not final, but we are looking forward to your comments.UIEnjoy!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hi, how about adding the option to select folders when creating a new movie ? Earlier we had the option to create a monthly video along with other options. I keep my photos organised in folders according to the month in my sdcard. Would love the addition of the older option or if a complete folder could be added when creating anew movie.Thanks</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Philip Penketh</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>From 3.1.A.1.0, you can see application's version name in the settings. Thanks +</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Love this app but wish there was a little more flexibility in creating own movies.1) select order of photos easily2) select which part of videos to show3) select the different lens filters on individual photos4) edit time for each photo to showApart from that it's one of my favourite apps!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Could you and bigger text window for notes. It's hard to navigate in this one-line.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Possibility to use filters for each phote on it's own?(of course with possibility to use one filter for whole video - as it works now)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Arda Erdikmen</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Movie Creator 3.1beta2 (3.1.B.0.3) is now available.Movie Creator 3.1beta2 (3.1.B.0.3)You can add your own notes to a photo and video.And we added new fade-in/out effect.Enjoy!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Adding more bugs/issues (using latest beta on D5803 z3c, Lollipop 5.0.2, 128gb sd):-when a new movie is notified and you tap it to open from notification screen, application crashes. (I cannot provide a way to replicate bug as I don't have any method to force MC to send a notification, but it happened twice in a week). After stopping the app, if you start it from it's desktop icon, program and movie works well.-When an old movie's files are not available anymore OR the  music is updated (?), the movie needs to be updated. But it looks like moviemaker picks same video for missing clips, resulting weird output. Note that phone is loaded with more than 200 videos (30GB), in both sdcard and internal memory. (it's better to disable highlights with missing clips rather than trying to rebuild it?)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Also possibility manualy rotate pictures/videos to the left/right would be fine </review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Great feature to create our own video, but there are some absences in Movie Creator 3.1beta (3.1.B.0.1):1. I took pictures of numbers from 1 to 8. As you can see from video I have tried to create my own video but while choosing photos/pictures to the video I marked photos from 8 to 1 but in movie it was sorted from 1 to 8. So would be fine if app remebers order of selected photos/picture.2. Following point 1. theres no possibility to order selected pictures. This feature would be better one than suggestion in point 1. Something like ordering playlist in Sonys Music app.3. After choosing photos/videos theres no possibility to add more one(s). If I forget select some(s) I have to delet current creation and make another one.Just suggestions after 5 mins of using :)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Thank you for participating in 3.0 Beta trial.Movie Creator 3.0 (3.0.A.0.6) is now available on Google Play!On Movie Creator 3.0, the length of Highlight movie changes depending on the number of your contents. Length is not limited to 30 sec any longer.Photos and videos will fit to the preset music when you change.3.1 Beta release is planned around end of June. Your feedback is always welcome.Enjoy new Movie Creator!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>What is today's update via google play about?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>   MOVIE FROM EXISTING PHOTOS/VIDEO    also would be fine to create video manually, from existing photos/videos.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>   CUT PHOTOS IN HIGHLIGHT VIDEO   Ive taken 4 landscape and 4 portrait photos and created video, but.... every single photo has ben cut to square form. I think I know what you mant by that (uniform image in the video) but it loks ugly. this video is just for testing, but in future (summer party, holiday etc.) this cutting could take of some nice experiences from highlight video.I would suggest add setting option for cutting or using original shape (portrait, landscape).if there would be this setting landscape photos/videos would be shown fullscreen and portrait could be shown with black stripes beside (expected result) or black stripes could be replaced by blur effect from video.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>   CRETING VIDEO GLITCH???    How movie creator choose which photos and videos will be involved in highlight video? Ive took 8 photos and record 2 videos in a row but in highlight video were only photos included. Why?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>   USELESS PLAY BUTTON    after exporting and deleting video from movie creator, theres still shown play button, but it has no functionality (besides that I can click on it with no result:D). would be fine remove it after deleting videos from creator composer.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Alan Dupre</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The first beta release will be available on 
<b>May 21st</b>.
<b>All android owners</b> can try this beta release. 
<b>521</b> 
<b>XperiaAndroid</b> Please join!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Magic Mo</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I have produced some great films with this app, such as this one from Valencia MotoGP race.I'd like better title ability and also to fade out music / fine image longer duration. As other have requested, to be able to select which part of a clip is used is my top request and also make longer movie please.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The movie maker needs to be longer. I made one as a music video but it just ends after 1 minute 47 seconds. If u can make the length longer movie maker would become amaIng</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Maybe position selector could be added into videos in highlight movie. App would set duration but user could set what part of movie clip will be shown.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Shuvro Mojumder (Nero White)</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hi. What about to ad list of highlights where could be  stored  all movies which could be created from photos/videos by one click. Even when automatically created movies are deleted, there would be stored infos for created those movies again and again until enough photos/videos are available for current movie. And if there were not enough sources for video, movie would disappear from this list. (I dreamed about this today, seriously :D)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>SiD Rhyte</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Teri Maria Cadano</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Took the bus just to drive a car</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>SiD Rhyte</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I'm excited to do this again, and yes, I can now create and choose multiple photos. I can also change the texture of pics also the background music. Thanks much! Will try a video clip next time. minna san</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Adam Tingley</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Seems like I can't add videos from my older phones, tried mp4 and 3gs or what it's called. It would be awesome if you could change the order instead of deleting and adding all over again. Please check out my new album  Extra Added Sugar </review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Konstantin Z.</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Rob Dyer</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Here my first video with the new beta version - I inserted the pictures in the order I wanted. It's a 'video postcard' of my day at an electronic music festival in London last weekend. (Music is added with clearance from the copyright holder).</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hi everyone. Thank you for participating this community.New beta version of Movie Creator, version 3.2.B.0.1 is just released!3.2.B.0.1On this version, we renewed welcome screen and list of other movies.We are looking forward to your highlight movie and feedback.Enjoy!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>raees shaikh</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>How to create movie</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Mahmoud Abd-Elatif Eldaly</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Amazing</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>SiD Rhyte</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hello. Happy to attend another beta, let's listen to the users as well as the professionals and keep it constructive. My main concerns at this point is the functionality of the app if you put it up against the move maker from the older generations. From the start I simply missed the feature to not automatically generate those movies at all since not all my photos are good memories, but still very important to keep for later reference. I love the features added to the beta, but it seems like I can't choose how mutch of a clip I want or how long each photo is on for. I absolutely love that you now can remove and change what goes on the move, and that you can select music is priceless. I have used quite a few video editors for computers, but there is no reason I can't use this app for my rather simple musicvideoes in the future if a few things gets a bit refined. Like for music selection you can set start point, but only to the closest second. I understand that eventually this feature will be available for videos, but if you can set points with greater accuracy lipsync would be within range. I understand that my needs are a bit outside normal, but one thing that I think everyone would enjoy would be to decide whether or not the audio from the videos are playing and maybe volume. I am yet to realy put it to the test, but I have used the app from the beginning, but never really enjoyed any of the movies until the beta features where added. Got to admit my life is rather tragic, but highlights from my life will be totally awesome when I can remove some of the not so bright moments since my phone is yet to understand witch captured moments I find beautiful and truly can be remembered as a highlight from my life</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Roy Rana</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Anu T Raj</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Creating creativity...</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>YoyaTG0 BIH</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hiii dali se ovdje radi ness ili samo nako hihi</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Hung Tran</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Jonas Rohde</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Stadt schloss Hecklingen</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Radha Srikanth</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>hi how to edit the pictures and add note to the pictures</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Could you add resizable picture picker? Something like in Album app is...</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user></user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Z3tablet</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Collier</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hi, can I create longer videos?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Thank you for participating in Beta trial.Movie Creator 3.1.1 (3.1.A.1.0) is now available on Google Play!3.1.A.1.0Google PlayThis release includes some bug fixes and improvements.Your feedback is always welcome.Thanks and Enjoy!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Could you add support for 4K videos (of course with quality compression while exporting to Full HD and lower)?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>We've promoted 3.1beta2 to the production channel as 3.1.A.0.5.3.1.A.0.5Google PlayThere is no big difference but some bugs are fixed. Your feedback is always welcome.3.1beta2Thanks and Enjoy!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I've tried to add text as note into photo (marked in blue) but only text, marked in green, was added...</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Since last update I have never got any notification even movies were created and even my notification in settings are turn on. Can you check it out?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Arda Erdikmen</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hello, I'm a video editor and a fellow Movie Creator user, and I think it's the one of the best apps on a xperia device. I'm using a Xperia z3 compact phone with 128GB sdcard.I experienced some issues (may not be bugs) since upgraded to MC3.0+:-I am using a 128GB sdcard on my device and MC is not selecting videos on a sd card. I can't say it's not picking any videos at all, but it tends to pick still images from any folder rather than my videos. My last 3 highlights entirely consist of images, despite the fact that I'm agressively recording videos for MC (my sdcard has more videos than photos). I know restrictions on videos, I always shoot at standard mode (no 4k or too short videos).-it starts to include Whatsapp videos and images, which is generally not related to my highlights, and there is no options to stop it.-it is just creates chronologically correct slideshows, old versions (and without using sdcard back then) was more creative, video based ones.-There is no menu item to check application version number.Thank you for this great app, and I'm eagerly waiting for next version.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Could you add into beta versions of app possibility to switch among languages? For example Im Slovak using Slovak language but for reporting issues, suggestions (for screenshots and screenvideos) would be fine english mutation to everyone understand (or majority). But possibility to switch them not just straight english :)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Movie Creator 3.1beta (3.1.B.0.1) is now available.Movie Creator 3.1beta (3.1.B.0.1)You can create your Highlight Movie to select your favorite contents.Dont forget to accept becoming a beta-tester from this link, please.Enjoy!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>3.0Movie Creator 3.0 (3.0.A.0.6) Google PlayMovie Creator 3.030Movie Creator3.16</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user></user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Saeed Haji Ghasemi</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>An ability for choose pictures from album for create movies</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>   REALLY MISSING FEATURES SO FAR FOR A LONG LONG TIME OF CREATOR TIME   *feature (idea) 1:can u add  plus  button between photos? reason: if i wanna add missing photo (not choose by creator app) I can only replaced with another photo. If app choose for example 12 photos in video can by only 12 or less photos (by deleting them).also this feature would be fine to add non-curent-mobile-taken-photo. example: if my brother send me photo from his Z2 (from the same event we spent) I can only hard add those photos to video (they are not selected by app) I can only replace with another photo as i mentioned before.same applies for videos too.*feature (idea) 2:just simple possibility to reorder photos/videos by taping and dragging to we could create our own time-line video stroy.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>   FIRST PICTURE OF VIDEO    how to erase/change these ornaments?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Movie Creator 3.0beta (3.0.B.0.3) is now available.Dont forget to accept becoming a beta-tester from this link, please.Movie Creator 3.0beta (3.0.B.0.3)Enjoy!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Magic Mo</user>
<date>2015-11-06</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text> The movie maker needs to be longer. I made one as a music video but it just ends after 1 minute 47 seconds. If u can make the length longer movie maker would become amaIng </review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Shuvro Mojumder (Nero White)</user>
<date>2015-09-28</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text> #MovieCreator </review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-11-16</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text> I have produced some great films with this app, such as this one from Valencia MotoGP race.  I'd like better title ability and also to fade out music / fine image longer duration.  As other have requested, to be able to select which part of a clip is used is my top request and also make longer movie please. </review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Movie Creator Team</user>
<date>2015-11-11</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text> Thank you for participating this community. Movie Creator 3.4 (3.4.A.0.3) is now available on Google Play! 3.4Google Play  This version includes some bug fixes and improvements from latest beta release.   Your feedback is always welcome.   Thanks and Enjoy! #MovieCreator\ufeff </review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-10-28</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text> Is this necessary? There's just one option after clicking on \ create\  button (first click). It could brings us directly into photo picker (excluded another \ same\  button but with different name(second click)). </review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-10-28</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text> Maybe position selector could be added into videos in highlight movie. App would set duration but user could set what part of movie clip will be shown. </review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-10-14</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text> Here's an idea. I was working to create a video with Movie Creator with 2 movie clips to include and it made an video of 5second length. Overall my 2 clups would be like 20ish sec long. So why can't i pick a lenght of an clip on my own? This last new update is great deal towards the end product, which i personally want to be like iMovies on iPhone, great stuff to quickly edit and make a video on your phone without having to transfer over to PC for a detailed edit and overcomplication. </review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-10-07</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text> Hi. What about to ad list of highlights where could be \ stored\  all movies which could be created from photos/videos by one click. Even when automatically created movies are deleted, there would be stored infos for created those movies again and again until enough photos/videos are available for current movie. And if there were not enough sources for video, movie would disappear from this list. (I dreamed about this today, seriously :D) </review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-09-30</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text> Thank you for participating in Beta trial. Movie Creator 3.2 (3.2.A.0.2) is now available on Google Play! 3.2Google Play  This release includes some bug fixes and improvements.   Your feedback is always welcome.   Thanks and Enjoy! #MovieCreator\ufeff </review_text>
</review>
</reviews>
