<reviews>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Why did you take off play-preview button? It was really great feature. It's step back and I feel disappointed :/</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Vasilis K.</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Facebook Audience ads??? Though I haven't seen any ads yet, the addon is there (checked with Addons Detector). Maybe it has to do with the fact that I have Facebook disabled, or that I own a Sony phone. I mean, having payed for a Sony phone and getting ads from a Sony app, is completely unacceptable! But if I start seeing ads, that will be the end for TrackID and for Sony for me! Get them out of it now!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Prasad Daki</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Please enable TrackID on the lockscreen....want it to start quickly without any lags....just like swiping the camera on lockscreen....</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Michael Davids</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>For some reason, whenever I move track id to my sd card, the wiget disappears</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Dillon Parrack</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>It would be cool if I could use the start track id by holding the home button and sliding it up to the track id icon.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Himalaya Dave</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>First shot my current theme,, 2nd unchanged navigation button.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Yonathan Perez Duque</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Because downloading function does not work?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Prasad Daki</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>New TrackID with Lollipop modification is showing slow signing in in our account in spite of fast connection...signs in late which can annoy when we need it quickly to record and identify a song....plz fix...</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Prasad Daki</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Plz add Jive link in TrackID...so if the song is available on Jive it can be directly downloaded....that will be nice...Can it search lyrics too? This will be awesome for it!!!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Dillon Parrack</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>It would be cool if there was a search bar that allows me to search the lyrics of a song</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>terry feng</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Love the new play button next to title to preview the song, don't have to search Youtube now.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Akini James</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Doesn't seem to recognise anything I throw at it, compared to shazam adn soundhound</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Himalaya Dave</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Past few versions updated without any changelogs !!!!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Himalaya Dave</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>While applying any theme and changing the navigation keys.The Keys remain stock in the latest beta version. Please make them able to change.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Himalaya Dave</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>What's New in the latest version 4.1.B.3.6???</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Do you plan something new?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Teddy Koursovitis</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hello to the team!I am not sure if it has been mentioned before but there a super annoying problem with TrackID on my Z Ultra. With nearly no exception to the version of TrackID the app every now and then reconnects to my account when I press the button to identify the music, instead of identifying the music. It's a big problem because when you are on a slow network or you are offline it takes very long to go past this stage. Note that I use a SEN account to log in and not Facebook. Please get it fixed, otherwise the app is gorgeous and the tag history is super useful!Thanks!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Is todays release beta or stable (not beta)?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>antoine naltet</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Here's 2 little ideas you might like...- Integrate Track ID to Walkman to search songs with the ease of a sentence while listening to music. Example Walkman, search this song for me. Bam it is found.- Integrate a add to Spotify button on track ID.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Ajo Philip</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Wish app had option to download album art, artist pics, etc so that same can be used in Walkman for updating album art /artist</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Giorgio Mignanego</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>TrackID non si riesce ad installare bene sui device BlackBerry, anche se si abilit il funzionamento da altre fonti software non BlackBerry (leggasi Android)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Khaled Badwan</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Here is bug? that I found with the UI in the new release.When you try to delete a song while holding down on the album art instead of a quick swipe, the album art keeps sliding to the left and doesn't lock-on at the edge of the recycle bin box, resulting in this empty white space as shown in the attached image.Also a suggestion regarding the track ID button, it needs a drop shadow effect similar to the lollipop Google+, Gmail apps write button</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Can u change this list into smaller icons. These are really place-taking icons. One third/fourth of size per song would be enough...</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Susanna Caleklint</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I can't install any newer version than 3.60.66 on my Nexus 6. Why?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Johan Liedholm</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Listen up all TrackID Beta users! Very soon we will release a new version of the app with a few things that we hope you will find improved.We would be really happy if you will help us out by giving feedback on primarily three areas:1. The randomized artwork for songs that are missing album art. We believe this make the experience a bit better than the current static image.2. The behavior of the app when data traffic is unavailable. The offline search has been there all the time but many users seem to have missed that offline (pending) search is possible. We have addressed this by improving the information when no network is available.3. The TrackID-charts is extended a bit more than the current 10 top items. The interesting variations in the charts actually happens a bit further down in the lists. Have a look and tell us what you think about longer charts.Of course we always appreciate feedback on things that do not work as well.Stay tuned, the new version is coming soon!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Gilberto Cruz</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Pueden esconder el boton de reconocimiento al deslizar hacia abajo, y tambien pueden hacer las barras totalmente transparentes como las aplicaciones de album o peliculas para que sigan el mismo diseo que las demas aplicaciones de sony</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>eva maria triguero hernandez</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Buenas noches comunidad</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Is todays release beta or final version? If final, do u plant release next beta versions?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>antonio masciullo</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>How I install it? Thanks :)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Christian Friedrich</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Just joined the test group...The Beta</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>missing icon of TrackID of latest beta version</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Carlos Flores</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>When will the wear app work with the latest beta?I love the new interface</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Jub Fabi</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The pixilated and misaligned issue has been fixed in the latest update. Thanks!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Cristiano de Oliveira</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Still poor resolution icon. Xperia T2 Ultra Android 4.4.3</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Luk Pvl</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>HelloI have this little layout bug. Except this bug everything is working perfectly.My Device:Xperia Z UltraStock 4.4.4 (14.4.A.0.118)This bug was present on 5.0 AOSP Lollipop too.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Little bit odd searching animation :D</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Vic Williamson</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I have decided to delete this app I am sick of waiting for it to decide to work or not, I have cleared creche turn phone off back on, tried with wifi and without not recognising even the most popular music not even when there is no noise and I'm stood two feet away from the source!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Cristiano de Oliveira</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>1 shot) Looks a poor resolution in icon. 2 shot)There are some problems, don't show the info completely. (Xperia T2 ultra)Sorry for my English.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Nico G.</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Used it yesterday in a noisy restaurant to identify song playing on the radio in the background. And it worked! Amazingly faster and able to recognize not well known songs than the previous version!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>rob haw</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>My icon has gone since updating to the beta version, just a transparent square now. Xperia z2</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Jonas Missiato</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Eric Hjalmarsson</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I found a small problem where the application just shows random letters and numbers instead of the songs name. See screenshot.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>ito 3500</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Excelente aplicacin la actualizacion fue de lo mejor ademas el diseo me encanta</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Yan Coates</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>It's blasting through whatever is thrown at it so far on my Xperia E1, fed it some radio in the early hours...remix filled...sailing through it...I'm gonna try some of my music collection later and see how it does there. Impressed so far though</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Go Xhiko</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Dnde est el link? Jaja</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>But I miss one BIG thing: offline search history. Yesterday I was lookin for some song which is in my history, but I was in no internet area (no wifi and only poor GPRS signal), so there was no possibility to check my history out. Can u add it? pls ;)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>jay lam</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Tried it on my Sony z1, playing radio through the speakers and tried trackID doing good so far.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Reyhan Alhafizal</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>- why newer trackid version can't recognize song from internal speaker? I like to listening to radio (in my phone). when there's a new song, I always use trackid recognize it. I keep use old version because the new version can't do this. please make new version can recognize song from internal speaker. I think users will love this fiture- trackid once had a text search fiture. but why was that fiture deleted? it's a very nice fiture. sometimes I know a song title but I forgot the artist name or I want to know the album title. with this fiture, i don't need to use 'tap to recognze'. I just need to search it with text. it's easier (and save more internet quota). please return this fiture.- I don't like the design of the homepage. I suggest to return the history menu.or if you can't (idk why) i suggest to change the design. I think it's more lovely if the album art smaller. so the album art arranged into 2 colomn. and the song title and the artist written below it. and also i don't like the- There's 'Search on youtube' button below the song's detail. I suggest to add 'Search lyrics on google' and 'Search song on google play music' or 'Search song on google' to download it :d. And add 'Search artist info on wikipedia' below the artist info.- Instead of our history, I think it's better to show our favorites artist' update, their post on social media, their newest song or video, etc. that will be great- In artist info, please add their post on twitter, facebook or even instagram. add their video on youtube.- I want trackid is not only a song detector. But trackid should becomes a place to music lover get the latest from his/her favorites artist.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Cheer Chunhao</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I hope I can get some answer for these two question although its not really related to the beta 1. Can we save our track history in other sites, maybe google+? (consider this as a request/suggestion)2. Is the app available to all devices and not just sony one? I only have a sony phone which is why I'm curious about this.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Dj Silent</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Good but needs a bit more!!Sony has music unlimited and not enough music that is found on trackid refers you to music unlimited. It seems like music unlimited and track id work off 2 different databases which is pretty silly. Sony products need to be more seamless</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Andrew  Marsh </user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Nathan L</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Ras. Tout fonctionne comme il doit. Les musiques sont vite identites et l'ergonomie de l'appli est vraiment bonne. Good job !</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Kashif Kamran</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Grant Flynn</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>How do I download the new beta version please</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>unknownC151A</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Look at the screenshot: Restoring history and later some random characters.Doesn't affect functionality but for qaqc?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Donald Kimaro</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I'll appreciate to be come a community member of TrackID Test</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Sachin Kalapad</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Its really feel good smooth n running butter</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>paul endri</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>V Jay</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Can you give link to become a beta tester</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Sean O'Connor</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I like the new design. It has a nice modern feel to it. Just a few thoughts:1. The profile icon serves no useful function once you're signed in. Why not move it into the other options section to sit above legal? 2. That signed in page says your full history is stored on the history page. The only place I can see my history is on the homepage, which doesn't show my full archive. 3. A search option would be great. After tracking a song, you sometimes want to explore similar artists. It limits its usefulness as a music discovery tool not having this. 4. More artist, album and song meta data would be great. Thanks for offering a platform to give our feedback.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Jonas Gyr</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I'm the only one who has the old layout on his tablet?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Yeison Y.C.</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Nueva actualizacin de TrackID beta a la versin 4.2.B.0.1 con-Sincronizacin de su historial de bsquedas en diferentes dispositivos con su ID de Sony o Facebook.-Compatibilidad con Android Wear.TrackID link PlayStore |</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Himalaya Dave</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Now its been very annoying to see ads.What's new now track id. Spotify its not available??? Please remove the ads.Ads are the most annoying thing. Are you going to charge money to free up the ads in the near future!!!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Khaled Badwan</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Track ID small appDunno if that was discussed or mentioned. Is it possible to have a Track ID small app for xperia devices? I think it would be quite useful!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Yonathan Perez Duque</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>hello, good afternoon .. a question: Is not prodra integrate option to download the tracks directly from YouTube?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Simone Sans</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>In app recent for Lollipop Track id is white.Do purple please</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>TrackID Beta</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hello everybody,We would like to understand how you prefer to start TrackID to find that song you're listening to.There are several ways to start TrackID, let us know how you prefer to do itby participating in this poll!Thanks,TheTrackID team</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Joseph Sing</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>What's the advantages of the Track ID app actually?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Prasad Daki</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>New TrackID with Lollipop modification is showing slow signing in in our account in spite of fast connection...signs in late which can annoy when we need it quickly to record and identify a song....plz fix...</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>RAPH &amp; MAX Gaming</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>This song existing nowhere ! What is this tag ? (if my English is not perfect, I'm sorry but I'm French)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Dillon Parrack</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I have to delete all of the songs I searched on the app before I can add a account</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Rudy Tantono</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Wheres the history? Before i updated to beta i have some history on main page</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>How can use this button. It's dead for me. Does it search music in google play?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Kashif Kamran</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>NA</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Himalaya Dave</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Nobody official (moderator) interacts here i don't know why. But the moderator should interact with the members so as to develop the app.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Luca Nebuloni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>ANIMATIONS.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Can you somehow re-arage it? ;)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Luca Nebuloni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>WE WANT THE ANIMATIONS! This app isn't alive..Go to see Google Play Games animations.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Tan Keeyong</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>It's would be nice if we can use track id for online streaming video or music. Eg, when I want watch YouTube video and use track id. The video stop when I use track id. Even if I use small app for it. The video just stop.It would be nice if track id can track the streaming video in small app method without stopping the video.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Sometimes happen when i click on search button in app it doesnt respond att all. i can just click on button but nothing happens.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Valentin Lopez</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hope this app was integrated to Walkman and that it also gave the lyric of the song and move with the song</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Jonas Gyr</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>it would be great if next to the youtube shortcut would be a shortcut for soundcloud :)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Can u do that small icon list of found songs from begining to the end? Those few first songs shown with big icons look very chaotic and confusing. Smaller list looks much more better and clear.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user> </user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>So why won't you make the navbar transparent as well (like in sony music and album) when scrolling? I think it would look more sophisticated.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>What's the clue of showing circle or square disc icon?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Kashif Kamran</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hello everyone!I will start withabig Thanksto all of you, foryour engagement and valuable feedback, we really appreciated that.As promisednew TrackIDversion (4.1.B.2.2) is released exclusivly for TrackID Beta Community.What's new in this release is as follows1. The randomized artwork for songs that are missing album art. We believe this makes the experience a bit better than the current static image.2. The behavior of the app when data traffic is unavailable. The offline search has been there all along but many users seem to have missed that offline (pending) search is possible. We have addressed this by improving the information when no network is available.3. The TrackID-charts is extended a bit more than the current 10 top items. The interesting variations in the charts actually happens a bit further down in the lists. Have a look and tell us what you think about longer charts.We really want to know what you think about these changes and overall experience.If you dont get the notification, go to Google Play to manually update:</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Samuele Farfarini</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I just joined this beta program and I stressed a bit the application: what I like most is the possibility to play most of the recognised songs on Spotify. I have the premium there and I'm not interested in using other platforms. However roughly 40% of songs played (from spotify) didn't had the link to spotify, which is kinda weird because I was playing them from... Spotify, on PC.Also, i found the recognition strong in particular on classical music if compared with other platforms (I mean, those software are NEVER good enough on classical, but I made a selective comparative with Google music search, shazam and soundcloud, and TrackID is the best one right now), but weak in everything else. It's weakness is particularly evident in movies soundtracks when there was no way to have recognised songs about ultra famous movies and authors, like Morricone, Zimmer and Tiersen. Even with indie music (always available on spotify, only tracks with rating &gt;40000) it has serious issues. No problem with famous rock and pop songs. Expecially with pop songs it's lightning fast, but the song has to be very mainstream. I suggest the killer feature could be a way to train it, like the possibility to give it a link with the source it wasn't able to recognise. (maybe from filtered sources, like Google play music or spotify, to avoid the risk to learn from a low quality content).(I personally developed a similar system for patent data mining and contextual search, and after 1 year of development without significant improvements, giving it the patent and make it learn from the source it wasn't able to discover was the best solution to improve the performance). Anyway, I personally appreciate the ease to use and the interface. I'm sure it has the potential to become one of the best software out there, but it still need a lot of work.I hope my small feedback could be helpful.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Riccardo Crincoli</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Manca l'immagine di copertina dell'artista Salvo Buono io non ci sto</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Abek Ramirez</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Wanna ask. Why is your database of songs for songs recognition or whatever you call that so weak? Do you plan to do something with it? I mean it in good way. Really like your app, but fr example it cannot recognize songs/ost without singing, only music. This concerns mainly soundtracks or songs, which is sung very little. Thx</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Riccardo Crincoli</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>L'ho provata e va tutto bene solo trovo che nella mini app sia fastidioso che debba per forza aprire l'app a pieno schermo,magari lasciare la barra ma che al tocco del logo avvii la scansione e mi scriva li cosa ha trovato</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Jaziel Garca Cruz</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>No estara mal que el cono de identificar desapareciera cuando se desliza la pantalla hacia abajo :T</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>TheFuturist -1-0</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Unico italiano?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>empty icon of TrackID widget; screenshots in next post</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Wanna ask. Why is your database of songs for songs recognition or whatever you call that so weak? Do you plan to do something with it? I mean it in good way. Really like your app, but fr example it cannot recognize songs/ost without singing, only music. This concerns mainly soundtracks or songs, which is sung very little. Thx</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>It happened again. Little bit odd animation.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Khaled Badwan</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Running the latest beta version. I noticed the following:-Track ID recognition button looks jaggy and pixilated as you can see from the screenshot taken from xperia Z3C. -Recognition speed is good, I feel it's faster but can be improved -So far prompt to sign in bug haven't appeared yet but will keep an eye if it happens again -The transition fade effect speed from page to page is not consistent.-In my opinion the icons in the top navigation bar menu are kinda hard to see at times. Maybe the background shade for the navigation bar can be darkened a little?! Thanks!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Kashif Kamran</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hello everyone!Thanks for all the valuable input that we have received from many of you!We have read every single post and based on your feedback we have corrected some issues and made a few minor changes.A new version (4.1.B.0.12) is now released to our Beta group. We really want to know what you think!If you dont get the notification, go to Google Play to manually update:</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Khaled Badwan</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The app keeps randomly asks for signing in. Whenever I hit the track ID button on the widget it starts recognizing the track but few seconds later it gets interrupted by signing in to my account! I missed few songs because of that, very annoying! I remember this problem has been happening even with the old version. Why can't we remained logged in, this problem was happening before with the Walkman app on xperia devices but got fixed few months ago.I'm using xperia Z3C and logged in using my SEN account Thanks!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I tried to recognize this song (</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Johan Liedholm</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hello everyone!Thanks for all the valuable input that we have received from many of you!We have read every single post and based on your feedback we have corrected some issues and made a few minor changes. We have also made a major change to the start screen. Now the history list will change into a more efficient list for the older items in order to easier find songs identified in the past.A new version is now exclusively released to our Beta group. We really want to know what you think!If you dont get the notification, go to Google Play to manually update:</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Elyes Messadi</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>This is the second time I comment and please let me congratulate you, it works very well with all types of music and even if before, it seemed to have trouble, it's really improved ( It can now even recognize Japanese songs coming from low quality videos, I must say I'm impressed ^^ )So far I'm satisfied with it, good job !</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Duncan Law</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text></review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Nico G.</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Would be Nice to be able to use other services to listen to identified songs instead of just music un limited. Identification is faster than in previous version. Would be Nice to have same design in all menus (for exemple id menu still bas the old look)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Nico G.</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Just downloaded it. Design is quiet nice and more userfriendly than before. Still need to test the most important part: music recognition...</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Felix XeZrunner (XeZ)</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I heard that the beta version of TrackID has Material Design. I used the link in the group description, I became a beta tester, updated TrackID but I still don't have the Material Design look. (Or is it only available on the Z series or something?)I mean I did notice some updates like the progress circle around the scan button now is more stylish I guess but it doesn't really look like Material Design or something.Xperia E1 D2005 Android 4.4.2</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>alex o</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Really fast compared to the old one. Still testing though.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Andy Branton</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Still trying this out on random songs, this one was off a pretty old tape that's not the best quality either.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Csar Ehuan</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Segn ya soy un Beta tester y no tengo la nueva IU, la app sigue igual! Is supposed that am already a Beta tester, but I don't have the new UI, the app keep as the same!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>cruz ruelas</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hola quien habla espaol</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Ram Attra</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Here is an idea.For a small in app download you could make the app work without connection, which would be awesome.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Erzsbet Fogl</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>letemben elszr van kezemben okostelefon Fantasztikusan j dolog</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Elyes Messadi</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Well, I tried it with some songs and it was not bad, I think better than the previous version, but when the song's not clear it has some trouble to recognize it</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>dave cody</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Works very well on te xperia z2 very quick in recognition of a song</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>It works fine form me, yet...</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user> </user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Feature request: will you return the option to save a sample of a song while offline so it can be checked whenever we get connection?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Adam Eckersley</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Won't login with Sony account.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Andy Branton</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Just became a beta tester and all's good so far. Recognised 2 tracks in seconds one of which was a cover of Johnny B Goode by Judas Priest.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Jonas Gyr</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>So... I don't know why it doesn't work... I have wi-fi on but it won't work. i hope you will fix this problem soon:)Sony Xperia Z3 4.4.4</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Mickal SSD</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Trs beau design !Pour ma part je trouve qu'il serait intressant d'intgrer</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Vic Williamson</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>It now does not recognise any tracks, what's going on?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Csar Robles</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hi! I want to congrats, the new TrackID app looks nice! Just I say some points that I find a little disgusting:1. When you a have a large history it's a little disgusting to scroll down to check an specific track, maybe a optional compact list view will be nice, or just a scroll bar.2. When you have a track registered in your history and you try to identify again the same track it will be generate a duplicated entry in the history.3. Sometimes when you launch TrackID from the widget it closes suddenly.4. You can't remove entries if you don't have a Internet connection.And here are some personal petitions XD :1. For Japanese music it could be nice to put the Metadata of the song in something more readable (the equivalent of the Japanese words) when the phone is not in Japanese. 2. It could be nice if there is an option to search about the artist in Google, sometimes I want to know about more of the artist.3. Put Google music on the options.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Michael Davids</user>
<date>2015-11-22</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Can you fix the constant need to sign in every time you go into the app?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date>2015-11-20</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>What about to support landscape mode in TrackID? :)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Martin Mrmus</user>
<date>2015-11-16</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>What's new about today's update?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>RaM Mohan (Mohi)</user>
<date>2015-11-14</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Integrate Track id app to music app so that it will have huge attention from Xperia owners..  Basically many of my friends are not using this app or by simply uninstalling them because of space consuming in internal memory, but if you integrate this app it will have huge no of access every week</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-11-16</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Can u give xperia users non-ad? So annoying</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-11-06</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>There's glitch of icons in fast memu. If you add small widget for TrackID it shows correct icon, but if you add big widget it shows faded Spotify's icon.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-11-05</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Could you resize also charts icons to be litlle bit thinner and more clear?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-11-05</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Possibility to remove/swipe away spotify connect suggestion. Don't need use Spotify so it's little bit forcing and annoying :/</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-11-05</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Could you add this feature back?</review_text>
</review>
</reviews>
