<reviews>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Juancy Rodrguez</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Lifelog not consistently capturing the built-in Movies app, Songza, Pandora, Kindle. Same issue as prior to Beta release.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Gary Paul Lynch Garcia</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>My smartband disconnects and reconnects automatically lots of times, with my phone inmy pocket, or even on the same table a metre away from me.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Randy Gleason</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Suggestion: Automatically disable night mode when an alarm is trigger. Should be easy to implement, it already has the vibrate option.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Antonio Frascogna</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hello +</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Fanny M</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Mine must have recorded Craig 's running times two, since I have not run at all! And please, if you could fix also the fonts issue... I can't see anything on my galaxy A3</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Patrick Fischer</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Beta Feedback: Widget is great but it doesn't actually refresh; only after opening the app (Sony Xperia Z3)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Valdeir Ferreira Camargo</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Why? Hwlp me</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Fanny M</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Feedback on beta version: still experiencing the same fonts problem. Can't see most text.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Fabiano Stanco</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Here in Brasil when i run my motorcicle it count as ride a bike and the location is not so acurated!!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Miczak noris</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Transportation works great on ma lg g2 mini good job!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Adam Poniatowski</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>High-five... for the person who broke it again. It worked fine, until today (which I noticed). I just saw that it asked me to sign in... which I tried. I reset my password to something else and it works, on my machine, the PSN app, but not the lifelog app... so... Either give me a fix for this... or give me the lollipop update... I am still waiting for that. Sony is now too Slowny...</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Shawkat Alam</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Sony is doing a great job with Lifelog app. the best ever app i used. Everything is just work perfect for me very nice. According to me it works very well with sony xperia phones.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Miczak noris</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I have question. How works transportation if i have turn off wi-fi, 3g and gps?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The beta concluded improvements but no new features wich is sad also a whist of my feedback and id ideas that my and other users give but maybe there will be a second beta</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Mark Lastiwka</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Since you can label home and work, I think it would be a good idea to have time at work at time at home as options. I would use time at work for my timesheet lol</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Analia Diaz</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>por qu no es compatible la aplicacin con Smart Watch2. en la Argentina es el ultimo que ha salido y me lo compre con la intensin de usarlo con la Aplicacin. una GRAN desilusin....</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Adam Madejski</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Mj Lifelog pokazuje totalnie bzdury. Jazda rowerem jako jazda samochodem. W czasie pracy gdy chodz po zakadzie pokazuje e te jad samochodem.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Robert Burbridge</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Lifelog doesnt recognize CM Browser as an internet browser, but a SocialMedia app (like Facebook). Cant even delete the log. Best solution would be the posibility to edit this and manualy assign program to a category (since it coretly tracks time spent on it).</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Ashok Kumar Kuwar</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>After recent update, the app has started showing my steps but only 20 steps the whole day.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user> </user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Lifelog app for android - when I slept at date time - doesn't see it on main screen icon (only night time sleeping). I can look all my sleep time, just if put this icon. Can't change position of icons on main screen and can't close bookmarks icon too.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I would like a quick switch boutton from GPS battery saving mod and high accuracy for the life log like a widget or in the notiflacion bar or even in the smartwatch 3</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Fabian Barron</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I'm missing a synchronization function for other wrist bands like fitbit or jawbone</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I would like the ability to refresh and load my activity data without having to connect to the network (wifi-3-4g) just like the Google fit app</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Juancy Rodrguez</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Still unable to update to the Beta app. I've included these screenshots to illustrate that the search results indicate an update available (that results in the system identifying it as already present - nothing ever downloaded). The Store app page does not show the update available.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Lifelog Beta</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hi FriendsWe are happy to announce our first BETA release!We have fixed some of the top issues:- Log-out issues, some users have been logged out without actively choosing to log out.- General stability issues- Reduced power consumption when using the widgetFrom your feedback we have understood that you would like to be able to use Lifelog also on any Android device, counting steps, measuring transportation and bicycling. In this release we turn on Activity recognition for any Android device. There are many devices and brands out there and we can never be sure that all brands/models has the same performance. We need your help - Keep sending us feedback!BTW have you started to use our Lifelog web application? If not go to</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Patrick Fischer</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Since the Android 5 Update (I think)the data on theSmartBand are no longer recorded correctly in Lifelog. I never walked so much this morning. Also running is completely wrong. It is very unfortunate because now the whole statistic is distorted. This should definitely be fixed; as well as individual data itself(or delete them).</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Phil Gautiere</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I would love to have the ability to change the unit tracking for running from kilometers to miles.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Kevin Brinkman</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>When will the tracking issues be corrected? I'm spending more time correcting incorrectly tracked info than actually having correctly tracked info. The app continues to change, everyday, running to walking after the next refresh. I now can't easily change the activity and it is requiring me to change every minute of the activity. Continue to be disappointed...</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Alex S</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Step 1: Join the Lifelog Beta Test community.  - ok!Step 2: Access Become a Lifelog Beta tester link to accept becoming a beta-tester of Lifelog  -where I need find this link?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Lonnie Stevens</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hello,I want to say that everything works great and i am verry happy with the app and my smartband. The only thing that goes wrong is that the app counts steps when i am driving in my car. I hope this will be fixed door</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Patrick Fischer</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Spotify Integration would be great. Or will be Playstation Music also be integrated in the Walkman App so that the music you listen to count in Lifelog.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Jean Paul Tomaz</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Everynight while im on ps4 lifelog tells me im both asleep and awake, important feature to fix</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Mark Gillespie</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hi, I have some feedback on my Lifelog experiences.  I own the following products:Xperia Tablet Z3 CompactSony Smartwatch 3Google Nexus 5The watch is on my all the time, the phone most of the time. Much of my music listening is via my phone.Obviously my phone not being an Xperia, means it doesn't log music listening, even if it was an Xperia, I don't want to use Walkman, I prefer to use Google Music all access, whic Lifelog doesn't monitor (at least not on my Xperia tablet).I also find that despite wearing my Smartwatch3, it doesn't track cycling. Apparently again, I need an Xperia phone to do that, which doesn't seem correct, as Google Fit tracks my activity just fine both on my watch and my Nexus5.I hope to see less restrictions in future versions of Lifelog, and embrace the Google apps more. (being able to read Google Fit data would be a great start)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Fanny M</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Also, there is another issue that happens regardless of the device used: the automatic night mode comes in even if you are walking in the street, therefore if you forget to manually switch it back to day mode (with the danger to forget to switch back to night when you go to bed) it appears as sleep time during which you are awake and does not count your burnt calories during all that time. I think it should detect when you are awake and moving and better adjust automatically the set night/day mode accordingly. But that maybe depends more on the smartband device than on the application.That has another danger: that you manually turn the day mode on at night , and then forget to switch it back to night when you go to bed: then it does not register you as asleep even though there is no motion for hours. Maybe it should automatically return to night mode when you are not moving and it is within that time frame that you set as night automatically. In fact, the instructions say it automatically adjusts night/day according to your motions besides the automatically set hours, but it doesn't do that, or at least it doesn't do it during the night time. It seems to do that only when you wake up in the morning it goes to day time mode even if it's still within the hours set as night in the automatic night setting.Other than that, I'm enjoying the smartband features.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Alejandro Barrero</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>How can I download my activity?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Adam Poniatowski</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>It's working now, thanks. I will let you guys know of any further problems</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Gary Paul Lynch Garcia</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I love the app, it's a great idea, but imagine having cloud technology working to its full potential. If I am a Sony consumer, it's due to all its devices and possibilties available. For example, I have an Xperia smartphone, meaning I have a walking Camera, so my photos that are stored in PlayMemories, should be available in my Lifelog also, and vice a versa. Also, if I have my Playstation 4, and an app that tells me how much I have been playing games, Why can't the Playstation connect to my SEN and tell my Lifelog that I have been playing for x amount of time? I have the app onmy mobile, it tells me everything, so it should be able to keep up to date with that too.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Kevin Brinkman</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Why am I getting credit for steps (not time) when I am driving?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I want the ability to change my activitys category like Changing the order of the activities</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Leonardo Torres</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>What s the Best time of the day to charge without compromising datalog?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Paul Humphreys</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>When I hit a daily target, steps or calories, I get a little rosette, which is nice but sony you're missing a trick here. These daily achievements could be gamified! What if when reach my daily calorie target I get some life log points or credits - these can then be saved up and spent in a life log shop where I can by stuff for the little white stick guy on the timeliness such as: a hat, some boots, somethings or a unicorn horn or a tattoo . Maybe I could buy a hammock instead of a bed or a motorbike or Lear jet instead of the camper van graphic. I want to customise my life log character and I want to be motivated. I will take the stairs not the elevator if it means I am closer to affording that cowboy hat I've been saving up for!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Aaron Lin</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Can anyone tell me when can I have the cycling mode in the lifelog?? HTC one</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Julien NICOLIER</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>How I can test the beta app, there is not a link to download it !</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>kirk lewis</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>It doesn't make sense at all. The watch has all required sensors included to track sleep. I assume Sony wants users to buy another gadget. It's easily possible to use Sleep as Android for sleep tracking. Sony should really think about changing that policy or some customers my buy a different brand next time.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Ashok Kumar Kuwar</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Anybody using this app along with a Sony SmartWear (Sony SmartBand or SmartWatch) and phone of some other coy (other than Sony Xperia)??? Please share your experiences here.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Kevin Brinkman</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Takes way to long to register a location and track. For example, I landed after a flight and drove home (1.5 hours) after I landed the app decided to update and show that I landed at my home.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Abel Agnes</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The daily average is wrong? I know that for the average, it doesn't count the current day. Without today, the 18th, the average should be roughly 9000 steps, not 6903..I have a feeling I know why it's off though. I went for a walk at midnight of the 17th with my friend amassing roughly 6k steps. My phone was on low battery mode so 4G wasn't on (but lifelog, z3, and smartband talk were still on). When I later charged it, my smartband talk reset to 0 steps. However, the lifelog app still included the 6k steps from earlier... But it doesn't count it for the average so I'm confused.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>In one of the lifelog commercials i saw a stairs activity why isn't it in the app?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Suyog Dhamale</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>After recent update app is using much battery.This was not the case previously.Please help.Location settings are power saving mode.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Steven Ng</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I like to suggest the following:1.  Allow users to download their tracking data (all of it) for save keeping and backup.2.  Would be good also to have the app be able to work offline line and data kept on local on the phone without needing to sync with server all the time.  Do periodic update to server only.3.  More options to customize the font, color, appearance of Lifelog presentation (incidentally, the latest copy of lifelog on my Note 4 Samsung has a transparent font in sub menus .. can't see anything!)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Antonio Frascogna</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>+Lifelog Beta hello. Just joined the community. I think the idea of lifelog is quite good, but suggest some important futures to enhance the fitness tracking capabilities e.g. closing the gap with GFit, endomondo etc etc.....1) add possibility to log sports other then running. E.g. you can swim with the band, but cannot record swimming 2) manually adjust steps if needed / add sports 3) improve recognition of public transport. App confuse bus with running. Using Samsung Galaxy Alpha</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The location traking give me worng renderings</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Bill Belfield</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Logging of travel is messed up since latest release, only shows last journey.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I can't stretch the widgets sideways to view more information please fix</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Nicola Horley</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I would like the option to add my meals and drinks to the calorie counter like Google fitbit and my fitness pal. Will that be a route you would think about?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I would like the ability to not have to share a photo with my activity you see I can't remove the photo</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Suyog Dhamale</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Sir,I have downloaded this app about a week back and till date the only parameter it shows is the calories burnt. All other parameters like steps, hour of walking, hours of running, hours of sleeping, etc are not recorded and are shown as zero. It also records communication and the photos etc.I am using Android 5 on Moto G 2nd Gen and there seem to be some compatibility problem. I wanted to try out this app before purchasing Smart Band SWR 30.Ashok</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Ashok Kumar Kuwar</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>If you use multiple launchers you aren't allowed to have more than one widget. Even when you delete the widget from the previous launcher you still get the alert. I had to uninstall and reinstall to place the widget again.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Randy Gleason</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Anybody tried the latest Social sharing feature in 2.6.A.0.10? We appreciate feedback on it to improve for next release./The Lifelog team</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Lifelog Beta</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Welcome to the Lifelog Beta group. We plan to release our latest features and explorations to you before it reaches Google play. We hope you like to be part and give us valuable feedback so that the lifelog product can be even better./The Lifelog Team</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Lifelog Beta</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The Smartband SWR10 is no longer working as music controller after lillipop .</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>fernando furquim</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>No deep sleep after upgrading Z3C to 5.0.2 (.690). Works fine under KitKat. Today I've installed latest beta and it behaves the same. Keeps wakelock all the time.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Sergiusz Roszczyk</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Is this some kind of bug? 33mins a day?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>vincent peng</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Feedback on beta ... still cannot see fonts !! many have experienced the same in different phones, this has been an issue for quite awhile already ... why is there no solution?? or even a reply from SONY?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Steven Ng</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Today activities recording seems to match reality. Still problem with fonts</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Fanny M</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Re-connecting is difficult swr10 w Xperia z3. Nfc seldomly works.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Karsten T</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Counting steps is not very accurate. Xperia z3</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Karsten T</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Beta feedby: besides not seeing the text, I was mostly sitting on my sofa from 14 to 19h, yet it recorded all these steps. I swear my kitchen is not that far!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Fanny M</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Why? Dont work anymore</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Valdeir Ferreira Camargo</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I like the faster syncing of data between my SRW 10 and the lifelog app, its much improved over older builds. However, every so often the smart wake up function will not work even if the setting is turned on. </review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Phil Gautiere</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Has there been any update I have not noticed? For some reason today it recorded three times as many steps as I did (I measured them with another app and with my common sense), infinite times more running than I did (I did not run at all!). The calories it says I burt match those steps and running that never happened instead of my real ones.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Fanny M</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I see there is a Sony Walkman Beta community too. Will it be possible to download this app on non-Xperia devices? The lifelog app doen't count music listening from stock android music player, so it would be nice if Sony made the Walkman (or soon Xperia Music) available for everyone. I downloaded the Sony Album beta last week, which worked fine, but since last update my device isn't supported anymore according to Google Play :(</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Alexander Verhaegen</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Checked accuracy of steps. Lifelog app upgraded version on Moto g 2nd Gen showed 175 steps against 330 actual steps counted physically. Also sleeptime shown on Smartband SWR 30 of my wife is 4 to 5 hrs as against actual 8 to 9 hrs on previous version of Lifelog. Couldn't check on upgraded version since cant download upgrade on wife's mobile. She isn't a beta tester.Hope requirement of internet can be done away for basic data.Otherwise a fine application. Well done Sony.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Ashok Kumar Kuwar</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>When upgraded version installed on non Xperia phone without connected smart wear, the steps and walking (which were not showing before) have started showing after upgrade but sleep is still not being recorded.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Suyog Dhamale</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hi FriendsWe now had our first beta release out for one week and we like to hear your feedback, specially on the activity recognition for non-Xperia phones.We created a survey that we like you to answer.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Robert O.G</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Yo creo que cuenta muy mal los pasos. Me cuenta siempre ms de 8000 y yo no camino tanto cada da. Lifelog +Swr10</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Erik vervaet</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>here's my feedbak. Pedometer the fog comes in, today I barely 400 steps Steps counter done gives me no less than 64 532 steps back. I work with the expiria z and with the SWR 10. sleep counter is + - well, if the pedometer is not intervening, occasionally I sleep and I walk according to the measurements, strange but true. regarding GPS, which calculated quite time at a glance, in other words, I drive quite a time on houses and water etc. pedometer also measures still participate with the result that the calculation is wrong if you have less than 30 km / h row is this counted as steps , walking or cycling. mvg erik</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Miczak noris</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Where I can find lifelog beta ?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Elvira de Bord</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The activity sleeping is never working. How can i use it ?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Nicola Horley</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The running part is incorrect. I ran for 41 minutes and it only said 23 mins.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Robert Burbridge</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The app counted steps while driving. In about 30min spent in car (15km), the swr 10 added around 500 steps. The GPS on map recorded corectly. The road was decent quality, so even if the pedometer has to count every move, than the system has to ignore it. Otherwise it might record in thousands when driving a really poor condition road.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Juancy Rodrguez</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>HEART RATE MONITORING!!!What's up with that guys? +</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Where's the new outlook of the lifelog app i download the beta didn't saw it</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Aaron Lin</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>My phone doesn't have 3G or 4G,I am wonder if I am out can I upload my record to lifelog(without WiFi or 3G)??</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Yolanda Iriarte</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Alguien habla espaol?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Patrick Fischer</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>It would be great if the Playstation game time could be counted. Would show me how much time I spend with gaming (sadly^^)</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Ashok Kumar Kuwar</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The issue of compatibility with other brand phone (other than Xperia),functionalitywithout internet connectivity (at least some important data may be made available), more reliable tracking specially/ sleep /steps/ distance etc and robust built without frequent failures are very important to be resolved prior release of Beta version.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I would like the ability to zoom in the life journal of the Lifelog app to see what I did in minutes to show more detail about my activity</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Alexander Verhaegen</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Please make it possible to edit the duration of the activities.Today I forgot to turn of Nightmode. After 2 hours I noticed, luckily it detected Transportation when I woke up. So I thought I delete the sleep-activity (2hours) after the transportation-activity, but this deleted ALL the sleepdata from this night :(</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Paul Humphreys</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>How about the swr10 gives hourly chimes so at 3pm it will give one long vibrate and then vibrate three times to tell the time?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Leonardo Torres</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I've done a 25 minutes walking exercise. At a rate of 120 steps a minute(I counted myself to test the app), it would be a 3000 steps in this period. Lifelog says I took 174 steps in 6 minutes. There is no battery issue as, after an hour, it's counting everything. During the excercise, the phone was in front of me, something like 30 cm. What could've happened?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>So the app tells me traveled 1336km which I didn't the GPS tracking is crazy wrong</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Kevin Brinkman</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Not sure what happened last night but now it is no longer tracking sleeping or running. In addition, barely tracking driving, walking, etc. I really wish this was a smart app and smart product. It seems to continue to get dumber everyday. There is a lot of potential for this to work with all Sony products as everything is tied together but that makes too much sense...I have reconnected my smartband (SWR10) to the phone (XPERIA Z3V) and nothing changed. </review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Josef Kopinec</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Skiing time= driving time? I understand, it is similar speed... But that is all what driving andskiing is similar. IfI can choose sport activity, it would be correct.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Fanny M</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I'm a user who just switched from Galaxy S4 to Galaxy A3, and I'm experiencing some problems with lifelog in this device.With galaxy A3 you can't see a lot of the text in lifelog because it appears so dimmed that it's impossible to read. The text affected is: text in the lifemarks, text in the amount of deep/light sleep, text in calories burnt in exercise/at rest, text in the weeky/monthly/yearly statistics, amongs others. For example, I can see the total amount of hours slept but not the amounts that correspond to light or deep sleep (see screenshots).</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user> </user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Lifelog app - Please makedark background during sleep time on the main screen with activity man, and hands changes about sleep time too.Will be very good if can put sport activites - choice kind of sport and Lifelog automatically count calories and movements if not use bangle that time.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Gary Paul Lynch Garcia</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Also, I have the google books, but my reading is not recorded.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Juancy Rodrguez</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Anyone else that there is incorrect categorizing of certain apps? I especially see this in games. It would be great to have the option to correct these auto-generated selections.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Daniel Eissler SirRobin</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>So what is the correct link for accessing the lifelog beta tester? is it</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>We need a new activity swimming it makes sense All of the lifelog products are water proof</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Paul Humphreys</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Went running this morning and it properly tracked the time. Now, after refreshing, the time originally listed for running moved to walking. Really? Just seems to be getting worse everyday...</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Kevin Brinkman</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Sleep monitoringdoesn't work!I'm using Sony SmartWatch SW3 +SONY XPERIA Z3. Is necessary downloadanother app? Has anybody the same problem?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Paul Humphreys</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I need some help. My lifelog software doesn't measure sleeptime anymore. I'm using sonys SWR10 wristband.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Josef Kopinec</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Phone (XPERIA Z3v) won't auto connect to the SmartBand after rebooting phone or turning off airplane mode. Have to manually do it.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Petri Ollanketo</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>More sports should be available like cross trainer, skiing, Golf. Also the activities should bei editable since the app doesn't sometimes recognise the activities correctly and hence the cal. consumption.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Kevin Brinkman</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I would like the ability to set an auto goalfor some days like in the week end i want my walking goal is 1 hour but other days i want it to be set for half an hour but I don't want to set that every week endi want the app to save my order and set it for me automatically</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Karsten T</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Wear something on my wrist with brings me no information is pointless. At least the watch brings me time. How do I monitor my sleeping hours? I'd rather test the watch. Do You have it in Brazil?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Using smartband talk with lifelog is amazing experience. But I'm hoping lifelog can let user customize which app is group within which activities. I'm heavily using other apps to READING &amp; LISTEN music everyday, but lifelog app cannot track these activities. It's a big disappoint to me. Example: NetEase Music app not record in Music activity.NetEase News app not record in Browse activity...Also, if possible, make it sync data with GOOGLE FIT app. If I install Google FIT app, there totally different set of data compare with lifelog.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Leonardo Torres</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Good night guys . How do I become a tester ? What is the link access ? I have to change the region of my phone because I 'm from Brazil .. ?On the link below 'm not getting ? Someone could help me ? am new ..</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Boon S.</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>the app is shit. When I got my Sony Z3, it worked. It showed me what I did during the day. Now it shows nothing... just calories burned... I sign up to this and I still don't have it working. Useless app, by the looks of things</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Patrick de Souza Teixeira</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Lifelog is not picking up my sleep pattern not cool dude</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Adam Poniatowski</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>How do i find the link to become a lifelog beta tester?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>kirk lewis</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>When I go to the www.sony/</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Gary Wilson</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Where can I find the link to become a lifelog beta tester?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>saad qarni</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I am uploading screenshots of my sleep tracker. U can c the sleep tracking is getting upgraded in batches even if the data is few hours old. U can c the time of screen shot on rt upper corner. Why should this happen.If i connect my phone to internet and I hit refresh then all the latest data should b updated at once and not in batches few min apart</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Gary Paul Lynch Garcia</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Sir,It seems that thesynchronizationbetween smart wear and the cell phone needs internet connectivity since the synchronization seems to be taking place through server.I would suggest that the synchronization between cell phone and the smart wear (band or watch) must be directly through the bluetooth even if the user is not within internet range. That would help people not carrying cell phone for jogging/exercising/walking etc and want to see the performance after returning back. There are times when the internet connectivity is not available for coverage problems.Of course if you need, the data can be uploaded on the server later as and when the internet connectivity is restored.Ashok</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Suyog Dhamale</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Any chance of an export option so I can open the data from lifelog in Excel and analyse it? That would make lifelog truly useful.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Ashok Kumar Kuwar</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Is there a way to change the measurements from kilometers to miles?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Michael Gerrard</user>
<date></date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>HI All. We just open the community and starting to accept signups. We will within weeks release a first Beta release to you with new experiences. We will keep posting information here.Thanks for joining, stay tuned./The Lifelog Team</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Markus Hebensberger</user>
<date>2015-11-20</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Thanks for the Livelog Beta. Now the traking of Music, Phone, etc works. And also the round icons appears in the upper display. Phone is an new Z3 compakt, paired with SWR10. The stock software was only showing steps, sleeping and traveling.</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Haris Xperia</user>
<date>2015-11-19</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Refresh data any time prosses how to fix it</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>Luca A.</user>
<date>2015-11-17</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Hello, can you add the record switch/button in drawer so we can switch quickly without entering in settings menu? Thank you</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>James Cullinane</user>
<date>2015-11-19</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Getting frustrated with no mobile data!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-11-19</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Counting stairs? Got my new SWR30 today and when I started it first I saw that stairway icon. Found that picture in the Internet with that kind of icon. How do I activate the counting of stairs?</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-11-18</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Dear Developers!  Travel time not logged. Please see the pictures! Lifelog works very fitfully for a long while. Sometimes log, sometimes not log: - Chrome, Google+and other communications app usage - Phone calls - Travel time - Media apps usage - While I listenig music, usually any other apps not logged  Please fix it!  Device: Z3 Compact with latest available SW and Lifelog</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-11-18</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>Can you link or connect sony smartband with/to other apps such as : Endomodo or MyFitnessPal ? Is Does the sony smartband work for the lifelog ONLY? Thank you!</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-11-17</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>I use samsung note edge + smartband2 + lifelog this app and smartband is great but When I call,listen music,watch movie or play game by my phone. this app not memo my activity. your guide tell me. this app can note all activity if I use google store's app My all app can download via google store. please check for devolope and fix this problem. Thankyou</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-11-17</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>The SWR50 is already sold...\ufeff</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<app_version></app_version>
<user>NA</user>
<date>2015-11-16</date>
<star_rating></star_rating>
<review_title></review_title>
<review_text>No sleep Tracking with SWR50? I just swiched from SWR30 to SWR50 to find out that there is no support for the sleep tracking... Are you serious SONY?</review_text>
</review>
</reviews>
